{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Excuse me, ___ which is the way to the station?",
      "a": "and",
      "b": "because",
      "c": "but",
      "d": "so",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- But: used to introduce a statement that explains why the thing you have mentioned did not happen or is not possible",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Truth is not true ___ it applies to everyone everywhere.",
      "a": "how",
      "b": "when",
      "c": "if",
      "d": "unless",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Unless: used to say that something will happen or be true if something else does not happen or is not true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ he opened the window, a sparrow flew in.",
      "a": "Though",
      "b": "The moment",
      "c": "If",
      "d": "Unless",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "\n- The moment = when",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "You should not despise others ___ you are rich.",
      "a": "while",
      "b": "when",
      "c": "because",
      "d": "that",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "\n- Because: used when you are giving the reason for something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "The world always will be the same ___ men are men.",
      "a": "though",
      "b": "unless",
      "c": "that",
      "d": "so long as",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- So long as: if, only if",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ he is no more, we have no one to fear.",
      "a": "Now that",
      "b": "So that",
      "c": "Unless",
      "d": "When",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Now that: because of something or as a result of something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ Jackson is industrious is well known to us.",
      "a": "That",
      "b": "Which",
      "c": "So",
      "d": "What",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- That: used to express a wish for something to happen or be true, especially when this is not possible",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Such was her beauty ___ everybody admired her.",
      "a": "as",
      "b": "that",
      "c": "which",
      "d": "what",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Structure:  Such...that",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "You should study hard ___ you should fail in the examination.",
      "a": "lest",
      "b": "but",
      "c": "that",
      "d": "when",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Less: used to show that someone is afraid or worried that a particular thing might happen",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It will not be long _________ we can have a trip to the moon.",
      "a": "that",
      "b": "after",
      "c": "until",
      "d": "before",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Before: earlier than a particular event or action",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "40",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}